[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the kanji '手伝ます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "てつだいます"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the kanji '手伝' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "てつだい"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the kanji '閉めます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しめます"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the kanji '消します' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "けします"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the kanji '開けます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "あけます"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the kanji '急ぎます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "いそぎます"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the kanji '待ちます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "まちます"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the kanji '止まります' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "とまります"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the kanji '取ります' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "とります"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the kanji '曲がります' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "まがります"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the kanji '持ちます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "もちます"
    }
]
